- [Instructor] In order to maximize learning
every topic comes with practical examples and exercises.
As part of this course, you will have challenges
and projects to test your knowledge
of the state management libraries
and also apply everything that you've learned
to push the learning experience a bit further.
And in order for you to follow along,
exercise files are also available.
For this class, there is a new way to access
and interact with the exercise files, which are Codespaces.
Codespaces is a code editor
directly available in the cloud with the full power
of Visual Studio Code.
You will see that this is very convenient
and everything is available and done online.
With Codespaces, it is easy to get started.
I will walk through through the steps.
So to practice along with the course,
you will have access to Codespaces
directly from the course page if you are already logged in.
Otherwise, you will be prompted
to create a new GitHub account first.
So the first time that you open up Codespaces
it may take a few minutes to create
a new virtual machine that we're going to access from here.
And once this is ready,
you will enter the Code Editor environment.
And if you're familiar with the Code Editor
of Visual Studio Code you will feel right at home.
This is a special and virtual version of Visual Studio Code
that you already know.
So on the left, there is a toolbar with a project explorer,
a search and a debugging feature.
Also with the options to do version control.
Plus, you have access to plugins
and extensions in order to add more capabilities
to your online code editor.
And because this is a browser,
it is easy to close the browser window by mistake
and to lose the editor but if you do that, no panic
because Codespaces saves everything that you're doing
on the virtual machine.
So whenever you go back to the editor,
it'll be exactly where you're left off.
So this is very convenient to work with Codespaces.
No development environment setup is required.
There is no need for tools or libraries installation.
Everything is ready to get started.
All you need is a modern browser and high speed internet.
One click and you're ready to go.
For every demonstration of the class
you will have access to the corresponding exercise files
with a starter and a final version.
And if you ever decide to start
at a specific point of time in the class,
for example, chapter two and video zero one,
you can always select the exercise files
for the corresponding chapter and video number.
And the tools you need to get started with the class
are a modern browser, high speed internet,
a GitHub account to access the exercise files on GitHub
and Codepaces and another tool, the React Developer Tool.
The React Developer tool is a development
and a debugging tool.
Very useful during the demonstration
and the development process because you have access
to the application tree of your React application
directly from the browser.
To inspect the state and the props
that you can see on the right left side.
And all you need to do is to add to your browser.
So you should read Add to Chrome in my case
because this is already installed,
you can read remove from Chrome,
but you should read add to Chrome
if this is not yet installed.
So you're now all set
and ready to get started with the class.